Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies fonds
1965 - 1987
F-23
5 m of textual records
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies
The Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies (FIDS) was established by the Board of Governors 12 December 1972 to succeed the Division of General Studies. The primary function of the faculty was to encourage the development of multidisciplinary and interdisciplinary programs and provide a stable administrative environment within which these could mature. Upon the dissolution of FIDS 1 September 1985, the responsibility for promoting interdisciplinary studies was inherited by the Faculty of Arts, and the FIDS departments and programs were assumed by the Faculties of Arts, Science, and Applied Sciences.
Upon inception of the Faculty, the functions of the previous Dean of General Studies were transferred to the new Dean of Interdisciplinary Studies. As the executive officer of the Faculty and an administrative officer of the University, the Dean of Interdisciplinary Studies was responsible to the Senate for ensuring that the functions of the Faculty were carried out. Specifically, the position was given six major duties: 1) to act as the central budget authority for all departments and programs in the Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies; 2) to administer all non-departmental programs of the Faculty; 3) to coordinate curriculum development through the faculty undergraduate and graduate curriculum committees and maintain scholastic uniformity; 4) to be responsible for faculty hiring, discipline, tenure and promotion in conjunction with appropriate departments; 5) to facilitate the research undertaken by Faculty members by ensuring facilities, equipment and support, and; 6) to engage in the ongoing assessment of Faculty performance through performance review, contract renewal, tenure and promotion evaluations. The Dean also acted as chair of Faculty meetings and represented the Faculty to external bodies such as Senate and the Board of Governors.
The Faculty consisted administratively of a number of departments and programs. Departmental chairs and program directors reported to the Dean, who in turn reported directly to the Vice-President, Academic. The Dean was solely responsible for overall academic and administrative matters until 1980, when the position of Associate Dean was established. The Associate Dean was made responsible for space allotment, the appointment of sesssional staff, the coordination of curriculum development in graduate and undergraduate programs, advice to the Dean on specific matters, and to take the role of Acting Dean when required.
The original Faculty departments were Fine and Performing Arts, Kinesiology, and Communication Studies, all of which were formerly units within the Faculty of Education. Fine and Performing Arts had been part of the Centre for Communications and the Arts; Kinesiology was an expansion of Physical Development Studies; and Communication Studies was created by the amalgamation of two former units: Behavioral Science Foundations and the Centre for Communications and the Arts. The original Faculty programs were African/Middle Eastern Studies, Canadian Studies, Computing Science, and Latin American Studies.
The Faculty expanded steadily in the number of its departments and programs offered. A program in Criminology was created in 1974, and became a department in the Faculty in 1975. Further program additions included Women's Studies (1976), Natural Resource Management (1979), Management and Systems Science (1980), and Gerontology (1982). When the Faculty was dissolved, it consisted of the Centre for the Arts; Centre for Canadian Studies; the Departments of Communication, Computing Science, Criminology, and Kinesiology; and the following programs: African/Middle Eastern Studies, Gerontology, Latin American Studies, Management and Systems Science, and Women's Studies. Upon dissolution, most of the units became part of the Division of Interdisciplinary Studies in the Faculty of Arts. The exceptions were the Departments of Communication, Computing Science and Kinesiology, which became part of the Faculty of Applied Sciences, and the Management and Systems Science Program, which became part of the Faculty of Science.
published
Full
Revised
Title of the fonds is based on the name of the faculty.
Fonds consists of records created and received by the Office of the Dean in administering the Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies (FIDS) and carrying out its operational functions. Activities and topics documented include the establishment, organization, operation and dissolution of the Faculty; liaison with other units in the University; the development and delivery of courses to undergraduate and graduate students; and the management of teaching personnel. Fonds includes correspondence, reports, agendas and minutes of committee meetings, policies and procedures, faculty case files, course proposals, course descriptions, and other documents.
The order of files was disturbed prior to transfer to the University Archives. The series were created by the archivist to reflect the operational and administrative functions of the Faculty.
Kimball, Meredith; Verdun-Jones, Simon N.; Calvert, Thomas W.; Brantingham, Paul J.; Brown, Robert C.
The records were transferred in eleven accessions between 1981 and 1987. Until 1985, inactive records were transferred to the Records Centre directly from the Faculty. Upon the dissolution of the Faculty in 1985, active records were transferred to the successor bodies, and then to the University Records Centre when they became inactive.
No further accruals are expected.
Consult the inventories of the appropriate successor bodies: Faculty of Arts fonds; Faculty of Science fonds; Faculty of Applied Sciences fonds; Department of Kinesiology fonds; Department of Women's Studies fonds; and the Canadian Studies Program fonds.
Access to some records in this series may be restricted, in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Please consult the unit list and the archivist for more details.
File lists are available.
- Administration and organization, 1970 - 1987; F-23-1; 25 cm of textual records
  published
  Series consists of records relating to the development of the Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies including its administration, organization and operation, and dissolution. Activities and topics documented include, but are not limited to, the establishment and operation of the predecessor General Studies Division; the establishment of the Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies; the hiring of teaching personnel; and the management of labour disputes. Series includes correspondence, policies, procedures, reports, and statistics.
  The arrangement was provided by the archivist.
  No further accruals to the series are expected.
  Access to some records in this series may be restricted, in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Please consult the unit list and the archivist for more details.
  A file list is available.
  - Division of General Studies - a review, 1970 - 1981; F-23-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 23-1)
    Textual records
    Pending review
  - Bachelor of General Studies degree, 1981 - 1982; F-23-1-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 23-1)
  - Establishment of Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies (FIDS), 1970 - 1971; F-23-1-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 23-1)
  - FIDS procedures, 1976 - 1981; F-23-1-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 23-1)
  - Senate Papers Relating to FIDS, 1971 - 1984; F-23-1-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 23-1)
  - Reorganization / Discontinuation - correspondence, 1984 - 1985; F-23-1-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 23-1)
  - Dissolution of the FIDS 1/3, 1984; F-23-1-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 23-1)
  - Dissolution of the FIDS 2/3, 1984; F-23-1-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 23-1)
  - Dissolution of the FIDS 3/3, 1984; F-23-1-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 23-1)
  - Internal Review, 1979; F-23-1-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 23-1)
  - Reviews of Faculty positions, 1977 - 1978; F-23-1-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 23-2)
  - Faculty requests and authorizations, 1979 - 1981; F-23-1-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 23-2)
  - Faculty requests and authorizations, 1980 - 1981; F-23-1-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 23-2)
  - Faculty requests and authorizations, 1981; F-23-1-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 23-2)
  - Faculty authorizations 1/2, 1983 - 1984; F-23-1-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 23-2)
  - Faculty authorizations 2/2, 1983 - 1984; F-23-1-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 23-2)
  - Records of Faculty appointments, 1986; F-23-1-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 23-2)
  - Promotion and tenure, 1979 - 1980; F-23-1-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 23-2)
  - Promotion and tenure, 1980 - 1987; F-23-1-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 23-2)
  - Promotion and tenure, 1983; F-23-1-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 23-2)
  - Teaching evaluation methods, 1980; F-23-1-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 23-2)
  - Personnel - strike information, 1976 - 1983; F-23-1-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 23-2)
  - Strike planning, 1977 - 1979; F-23-1-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 23-2)
  - Departmental statistics, 1977; F-23-1-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 23-2)
  - Dean's Office - academic discipline, 1983 - 1984; F-23-1-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 23-2)
  - Grading proposal, 1977; F-23-1-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 23-2)
  - Research policies, 1977 - 1980; F-23-1-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 23-2)
- Dean's office correspondence, 1971 - 1985; F-23-2; 79 cm of textual records
  Records relating to the functions of the Dean as the chief officer of the Faculty. Activities and topics documented include, but are not limited to, the hiring of faculty and staff; curriculum development and delivery; university and faculty organization; policies and procedures; budgetary decisions; equipment and space allocation; and student matters such as grading policies. Series consists primarily of correspondence, but includes some reports, proposals and other types of documents.
  - Dean's correspondence, 1971 - 1977; F-23-2-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 23-3)
  - Dean's correspondence, 1977 - 1980; F-23-2-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 23-3)
  - Dean's correspondence with Chairs and Directors, 1972 - 1977; F-23-2-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 23-3)
  - Dean's correspondence with Chairs and Directors, 1977 - 1980; F-23-2-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 23-3)
  - Dean's correspondence with Chairs and Directors, 1981 - 1984; F-23-2-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 23-3)
  - Associate Dean's correspondence, 1982; F-23-2-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 23-3)
  - Correspondence: President, 1971 - 1972; F-23-2-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 23-3)
  - Correspondence: President, 1971 - 1972; F-23-2-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 23-3)
  - Correspondence: President, 1972 - 1974; F-23-2-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 23-3)
  - Correspondence: President, 1974 - 1975; F-23-2-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 23-3)
  - [Empty], F-23-2-0-0-11
  - Correspondence: President, 1975 - 1980; F-23-2-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 23-4)
  - Correspondence: President, 1979 - 1980; F-23-2-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 23-4)
  - Correspondence: President, 1981 - 1982; F-23-2-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 23-4)
  - Correspondence: President, 1983 - 1985; F-23-2-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 23-4)
  - Correspondence: Vice-President, Academic, 1971 - 1972; F-23-2-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 23-4)
  - Correspondence: Vice-President, Academic, 1972 - 1973; F-23-2-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 23-4)
  - Correspondence: Vice-President, Academic, 1972 - 1974; F-23-2-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 23-4)
  - Correspondence: Vice-President, Academic, 1974 - 1975; F-23-2-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 23-4)
  - Correspondence: Vice-President, Academic, 1976 - 1977; F-23-2-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 23-5)
  - Correspondence: Vice-President, Academic, 1972 - 1980; F-23-2-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 23-5)
  - Correspondence: Vice-President, Academic, 1980 - 1982; F-23-2-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 23-5)
  - Correspondence: Vice-President, Academic, 1981 - 1983; F-23-2-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 23-5)
  - Correspondence: Vice-President, Academic, 1983 - 1985; F-23-2-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 23-5)
  - Correspondence: Vice-President, Academic - Dean's retreats, 1980 - 1982; F-23-2-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 23-5)
  - Correspondence: Vice-President, Academic - policies and procedures, 1978 - 1982; F-23-2-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 23-6)
  - Correspondence: Associate Vice-President, Academic, 1981 - 1982; F-23-2-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 23-6)
  - Correspondence: Associate Vice-President, Academic, 1983 - 1985; F-23-2-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 23-6)
  - Correspondence: Assistant to Vice-President, Academic, 1973 - 1977; F-23-2-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 23-6)
  - Correspondence: Assistant to Vice-President, Academic, 1980 - 1983; F-23-2-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 23-6)
  - Correspondence: Vice-President, Administration, 1977 - 1980; F-23-2-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 23-6)
  - Correspondence: Vice-President, Administration, 1971 - 1976; F-23-2-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 23-6)
  - Correspondence: Vice-President, Administration, 1981 - 1983; F-23-2-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 23-6)
  - Correspondence: Vice-President, University Development and Extension, 1982 - 1985; F-23-2-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 23-6)
  - Correspondence: Arts, Dean of, 1972 - 1981; F-23-2-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 23-6)
  - Correspondence: Arts, Dean of, 1985; F-23-2-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 23-6)
  - Correspondence: Graduate Studies, Dean of, 1972 - 1973; F-23-2-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 23-6)
  - Correspondence: Graduate Studies, Dean of, 1974 - 1976; F-23-2-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 23-6)
  - Correspondence: Graduate Studies, Dean of, 1976 - 1981; F-23-2-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 23-6)
  - Correspondence: Science, Dean of, 1971 - 1985; F-23-2-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 23-6)
  - Correspondence: Analytical Studies - miscellaneous, 1972 - 1978; F-23-2-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 23-6)
  - Correspondence: Analytical Studies - space allocation, 1982; F-23-2-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 23-6)
  - Correspondence: Analytical Studies - space allocation, 1983; F-23-2-0-0-43 (Archival box - small 23-7)
  - Correspondence: Analytical Studies - space allocation, 1982 - 1984; F-23-2-0-0-44 (Archival box - small 23-7)
  - Correspondence: Animal Care Facility, 1977 - 1980; F-23-2-0-0-45 (Archival box - small 23-7)
  - Correspondence: Computing Centre, 1978 - 1984; F-23-2-0-0-46 (Archival box - small 23-7)
  - Correspondence: Communication Studies, 1975 - 1976; F-23-2-0-0-47 (Archival box - small 23-7)
  - Correspondence: Continuing Studies, 1976 - 1982; F-23-2-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 23-8)
  - Correspondence: Continuing Studies, 1983; F-23-2-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 23-8)
  - Correspondence: Education, Faculty of, 1972 - 1976; F-23-2-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 23-8)
  - Correspondence: Engineering 1/2, 1981 - 1982; F-23-2-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 23-8)
  - Correspondence: Engineering 2/2, 1981 - 1982; F-23-2-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 23-8)
  - Correspondence: Engineering, 1982 - 1983; F-23-2-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 23-8)
  - Correspondence: Finance, 1984; F-23-2-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 23-8)
  - Correspondence: Geography, 1972 - 1982; F-23-2-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 23-8)
  - Correspondence: History, 1971 - 1976; F-23-2-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 23-8)
  - Correspondence: Languages, Literatures and Linguistics, 1975 - 1976; F-23-2-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 23-8)
  - Correspondence: Mathematics, 1972; F-23-2-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 23-8)
  - Correspondence: Physical Plant and Planning, 1971 - 1981; F-23-2-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 23-8)
  - Correspondence: Physics, 1975; F-23-2-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 23-8)
  - Correspondence: Political Science, 1971 - 1975; F-23-2-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 23-8)
  - Correspondence: Psychology, 1972; F-23-2-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 23-8)
  - Correspondence: Registrar's Office, 1982 - 1983; F-23-2-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 23-8)
  - Correspondence: Registrar's Office, 1982 - 1985; F-23-2-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 23-8)
- Departmental / program affairs, 1970 - 1985; F-23-3; 1.19 m of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the ongoing activities of each department or program within the Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies. Activities and topics documented include, but are not limited to, liaison of the Dean's Office with individual departments and program areas within the Faculty; departmental organization and governance; development and delivery of courses; the hiring, promotion, and awarding of tenure to faculty members; selection of chairpersons; research projects, centres and institutes; budgetary decisions; and university reviews of departmental performance. Not all of these activities are documented for each department or program area. Series includes correspondence, reports, proposals, working papers, agendas, minutes, statistics, and other documents. Addition of a sub-series in May 2004 includes records documenting the Africa/Middle East Studies program.
  - Area Studies, 1977 - 1983; F-23-3-1; 7 cm of textual records
    No further accruals to the sub-series are expected.
    Some files contain personal information; access to these files may be restricted to protect the privacy of individuals. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
    - African/Middle East Studies, 1978 - 1983; F-23-3-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 23-8)
    - Canadian Studies, 1977 - 1979; F-23-3-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 23-8)
    - Canadian Studies, 1980; F-23-3-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 23-8)
    - Canadian Studies, 1981 - 1983; F-23-3-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 23-9)
    - Institute of Fisheries Analysis, 1979 - 1980; F-23-3-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 23-9)
    - Institute of Fisheries Analysis, 1981 - 1983; F-23-3-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 23-9)
    - Latin American Studies, 1977 - 1981; F-23-3-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 23-9)
      Open
    - Latin American Studies, 1982 - 1983; F-23-3-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 23-9)
  - Centre for the Arts, 1970 - 1982; F-23-3-2; 7 cm of textual records
    - Centre for the Arts, 1972; F-23-3-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 23-9)
    - Centre for the Arts, 1975 - 1976; F-23-3-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 23-9)
    - Centre for the Arts, 1977 - 1981; F-23-3-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 23-9)
    - Centre for the Arts, 1981 - 1982; F-23-3-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 23-9)
    - Dance program, 1970 - 1974; F-23-3-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 23-9)
    - Consultant's report, 1974; F-23-3-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 23-9)
    - Leonardo project - computer graphics, 1977; F-23-3-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 23-9)
  - Communication Studies, 1971 - 1985; F-23-3-3; 20 cm of textual records
    - General correspondence, 1971 - 1972; F-23-3-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 23-9)
    - General correspondence, 1972 - 1985; F-23-3-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 23-10)
    - General correspondence, 1973; F-23-3-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 23-10)
    - General correspondence, 1973 - 1976; F-23-3-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 23-10)
    - General correspondence, 1977 - 1980; F-23-3-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 23-10)
    - General correspondence, 1979 - 1982; F-23-3-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 23-10)
    - General correspondence, 1983 - 1985; F-23-3-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 23-10)
    - Departmental meeting agendas and minutes, 1973 - 1974; F-23-3-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 23-10)
    - Departmental tenure/appointments committee, 1974 - 1984; F-23-3-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 23-10)
    - Graduate and undergraduate studies committee, 1973 - 1975; F-23-3-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 23-11)
    - Faculty workloads, 1971 - 1978; F-23-3-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 23-11)
    - Research activity, 1977 - 1982; F-23-3-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 23-11)
    - PEACESAT satellite radio, 1978 - 1979; F-23-3-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 23-11)
    - Telecommunications research group, 1973 - 1976; F-23-3-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 23-11)
    - Telecommunications research group, 1977 - 1980; F-23-3-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 23-11)
  - Computing Science, 1970 - 1985; F-23-3-4; 18 cm of textual records
    - General correspondence, 1971 - 1972; F-23-3-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 23-11)
    - General correspondence, 1973 - 1976; F-23-3-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 23-11)
    - General correspondence, 1977 - 1980; F-23-3-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 23-11)
    - General correspondence, 1977 - 1982; F-23-3-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 23-11)
    - General correspondence, 1981; F-23-3-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 23-11)
    - General correspondence, 1982; F-23-3-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 23-12)
    - General correspondence, 1982 - 1983; F-23-3-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 23-12)
    - General correspondence, 1984 - 1985; F-23-3-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 23-12)
    - Departmental meeting minutes, 1983; F-23-3-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 23-12)
    - Departmental tenure committee, 1973 - 1984; F-23-3-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 23-12)
    - Steering committee, 1972 - 1977; F-23-3-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 23-12)
    - Lab for computer and communications research, 1982 - 1985; F-23-3-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 23-12)
    - Curriculum, 1970 - 1972; F-23-3-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 23-12)
    - Curriculum, 1970 - 1973; F-23-3-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 23-12)
    - Curriculum, 1971; F-23-3-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 23-12)
    - Curriculum, 1972; F-23-3-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 23-12)
  - Criminology, 1971 - 1983; F-23-3-5; 11 cm of textual records
    - Director's correspondence, 1974 - 1975; F-23-3-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 23-13)
    - General correspondence, 1973 - 1976; F-23-3-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 23-13)
    - General correspondence, 1977 - 1980; F-23-3-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 23-13)
    - General correspondence, 1981 - 1982; F-23-3-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 23-13)
    - Departmental governance and meetings, 1977 - 1978; F-23-3-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 23-13)
    - Establishment of Criminology program, 1971 - 1973; F-23-3-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 23-13)
    - Establishment of Criminology program, 1972 - 1973; F-23-3-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 23-13)
    - Establishment of Criminology program, 1972 - 1974; F-23-3-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 23-13)
    - Funding - general, 1972 - 1976; F-23-3-5-0-9 (Archival box - standard 23-13)
    - Funding - federal, 1975 - 1978; F-23-3-5-0-10 (Archival box - standard 23-13)
    - Criminology research centre, 1977 - 1980; F-23-3-5-0-11 (Archival box - standard 23-13)
    - Criminology research centre, 1981 - 1983; F-23-3-5-0-12 (Archival box - standard 23-13)
    - Directed independent study courses, 1978 - 1981; F-23-3-5-0-13 (Archival box - standard 23-13)
    - Institute for Studies in Criminal Justice, 1980 - 1983; F-23-3-5-0-14 (Archival box - standard 23-13)
  - Gerontology, 1982 - 1983; F-23-3-6; 1 cm of textual records
    - General correspondence, 1982 - 1983; F-23-3-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 23-13)
  - Kinesiology, 1971 - 1985; F-23-3-7; 25 cm of textual records